A Guide to the The Road Company Records, 1972-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Besson Hall, 1993. (Box-folder 19-31 to 19-32 (2 folders))
- Release Forms, 1993. (Box-folder 19-33)
- Annual Meeting, 1993. (Box-folder 19-34)
- Beeson Hall and Fever, 1993. (Box-folder 19-35)
- IBM, 1993. (Box-folder 19-36)
- Annual Meeting, 1993. (Box-folder 19-37)
- General Mills, 1993. (Box-folder 19-38)
- New Show, 1993. (Box-folder 19-39)
- SELMA--Tax Forms, 1993. (Box-folder 19-40)
- James Hanes Memorial Fund and Foundation, 1993. (Box-folder 19-41)
- William B. Stokely Jr. Foundation, 1993. (Box-folder 19-42)
- Contract for Tour to Bashkortostan, 1993. (Box-folder 19-43)
- Art Auction Inventory Forms, 1993. (Box-folder 19-44)
- Gloucester Stage Company, 1993. (Box-folder 19-45)
- The Bear Facts, 1993. (Box-folder 19-46)
- Application for Grants, 1993. (Box-folder 19-47)
- Bear Facts, 1993. (Box-folder 19-48 to 19-49 (2 folders))
- SAF--John O'Neal, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-50)
- Chicago Resource Center, Speak Up Now, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-51)
- NEA International Projects, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-52)
- NEA Theater, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-53)
- Road Company Art Information, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-54)
- Box Office, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-55)
- Board Minutes, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-56)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Grants, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-57)
- Time Sheets, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-58)
- Junebug Productions, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-59)
- Contribution Campaign, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-60)
- Arts Build Communities: Grants, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-61)
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Technical Assistance, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-62)
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Grants, 1993-1994. (Box-folder 19-63)
- Reservations, 1994. (Box-folder 20-1)
- Quillen Pictures, 1994. (Box-folder 20-2)
- Bidding and Abetting, 1994. (Box-folder 20-3)
- Audited Financial Statement, 1994. (Box-folder 20-4)
- Echoes Science Hill Project, 1994. (Box-folder 20-5)
- AG Awards, 1994. (Box-folder 20-6)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Testimony, 1994. (Box-folder 20-7)
- Selma Project, 1994. (Box-folder 20-8)
- Eugene Wolf Agreement, 1994. (Box-folder 20-9)
- Human Race, 1994. (Box-folder 20-10)
- Art Auction--Miscellaneous, 1994. (Box-folder 20-11)
- Annual Meeting, 1994. (Box-folder 20-12)
- Residency of Jane Goldberg, 1994. (Box-folder 20-13)
- Residency of John O'Neal, 1994. (Box-folder 20-14)
- Residency of Jon Spelman, 1994. (Box-folder 20-15)
- Pictures of Art Auction, 1994. (Box-folder 20-16)
- Pictures of "Oleanna," 1994. (Box-folder 20-17)
- "Oleanna" Show Dates, 1994. (Box-folder 20-18)
- Rights for "Blind Desire," 1994. (Box-folder 20-19)
- Pictures of "Zero Moment," 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-20)
- Box Office Statements, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-21)
- Miscellaneous, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-22)
- Board Meeting, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-23)
- Fundraising Campaign, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-24 to 20-25 (2 folders))
- Touring Information, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-26)
- Grants Related to National Endowment for the Arts, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-27)
- Virginia Tech Small Grant Expenditures, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-28)
- Expenditures Related to the Tennessee Arts Commission (40130), 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-29)
- Expenditures Related to the National Endowment for the Arts (40120), 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-30)
- Expenditures Related to the National Endowment for the Arts Grant (40110), 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-31)
- Expansion Arts Grant from National Endowment for the Arts, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-32)
- Arts Build Communities Grant, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-33)
- Art Auction, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 20-34 to 20-35 (2 folders))
- Artist in Residence Program, 1994-1996. (Box-folder 20-36)
- Board Duties, 1994-1996. (Box-folder 20-37)
- Cumberland County Playhouse, 1995. (Box-folder 20-38)
- Annual Meeting, 1995. (Box-folder 20-39)
- Touchstone Theater's "Fish," 1995. (Box-folder 20-40)
- Hiddenite Center, 1995. (Box-folder 20-41)
- Miscellaneous, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-42)
- Bidding and Abetting, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-43)
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Grants, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-44)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Grants, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-45)
- Roots Touring Application, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-46)
- Tennessee Arts Performing Center, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-47)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Expansion Arts Program, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-48)
- Fundraising Campaign, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-49)
- Art Auction Information, 1995-1996. (Box-folder 20-50)
- Expansion Arts, 1995-1997. (Box-folder 20-51)
- General Mills, 1996. (Box-folder 21-1)
- Pictures from "Blind Desire," 1996. (Box-folder 21-2)
- Radio Show and Contributions, 1996. (Box-folder 21-3)
- "Southern Exposure," 1996. (Box-folder 21-4)
- Semester Information on Greece and Turkey, 1996. (Box-folder 21-5)
- Production Programs and Reviews, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-6)
- Box Office Statements, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-7)
- NEA Expansion Arts, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-8)
- NEA Theater, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-9)
- TAC, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-10)
- ABC, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 21-11)
- Board Meetings, 1996-1998. (Box-folder 21-12)
- Roll Sheets, 1997. (Box-folder 21-13)
- Beeson Hall Community Arts Center, 1997. (Box-folder 21-14)
- HTELAC Rights, 1997. (Box-folder 21-15)
- Beeson Play, 1997. (Box-folder 21-16)
- The Road Company Rag, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-17)
- Box Office, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-18)
- NEA Constitution, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-19)
- ABC, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-20)
- TAC, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-21)
- NEA, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 21-22)
- Stopping, 1998. (Box-folder 21-23)
- NEA Consortium, 1998-1999. (Box-folder 21-24)
- Industries (Box-folder 22-1)
- Stage Manager's Production Notes (Box-folder 22-2)
- One Potato, Two Technical Notes (Box-folder 22-3)
- Corporate Fundraising (Box-folder 22-4 to 22-5 (2 folders))
- Corner Rooms Promotional Work (Box-folder 22-6)
- Heroes Program (Box-folder 22-7)
- Financial Brochure (Box-folder 22-8)
- Pictures from "Little Chicago," (Box-folder 22-9 to 22-10 (2 folders))
- National Endowment for the Arts: Institutional Advancement Grants (Box-folder 22-11)
- Pictures from "Vanities," (Box-folder 22-12)
- Pictures from "Further Adventures of Sally," (Box-folder 22-13)
- Pictures from "Blind Desire," (Box-folder 22-14)
- Equity Information (Box-folder 22-15)
- Scripts (Box-folder 22-16)
- Miscellaneous Notes (Box-folder 22-17)
- Activities for Artists in School Programs (Box-folder 22-18)
- Artists in Residence Program (Box-folder 22-19)
- First People's Bank Checkbook (Box-folder 22-20)
- Stage Manager's Notes for "Little Chicago," (Box-folder 22-21)
- Promethens Bibliography (Box-folder 22-22)
- Americomedia Revolutionary Posters (Box-folder 22-23)
- American Revolutionary Road Company Information (Box-folder 22-24)
- Other Companies Brochures (Box-folder 22-25)
- Closet Art Show (Box-folder 22-26)
- Valentine's Dance (Box-folder 22-27)
- Promotional and General Mailing List (Box-folder 22-28)
- Untitled Play (Box-folder 22-29)
- Something Entirely New (Box-folder 22-30)
- Cue Sheets (Box-folder 22-31)
- Various Reading Material (Box-folder 22-32)
- Happy Birthday Board Cues (Box-folder 22-33)
- Goddess Production Information (Box-folder 22-34)
- Miscellaneous Research Materials (Box-folder 22-35)
- Make Object a Hero (Box-folder 22-36)
- Miscellaneous Essays (Box-folder 22-37)
- Miscellaneous Manuscripts (Box-folder 22-38)
- Correspondence Copies (Box-folder 22-39)
- Silent Auction Bids. (Box-folder 23-1)
- Presenting Possibilities. (Box-folder 23-2)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 23-3 to 23-5 (3 folders))
- Time Sheet. (Box-folder 23-6)
- Neighborhood Projects. (Box-folder 23-7)
- Technical Information. (Box-folder 23-8)
- Student Plays. (Box-folder 23-9)
- Equipment Manuals. (Box-folder 23-10)
- Miscellaneous Information about The Road Company. (Box-folder 23-11)
- Columbus Project Projected Costs. (Box-folder 23-12)
- The Road Company History. (Box-folder 23-13)
- Mission Statement. (Box-folder 23-14)
- New Show Budget. (Box-folder 23-15)
- List of Organizations. (Box-folder 23-16)
- Tour Agent. (Box-folder 23-17)
- Southern Arts Federation Information. (Box-folder 23-18)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 23-19)
- Questions for Mr. Know It All. (Box-folder 23-20)
- Teen Pregnancy Materials. (Box-folder 23-21)
- Theater Brochures. (Box-folder 23-22)
- Miscellaneous News Clippings and Information. (Box-folder 23-23)
- To be filed. (Box-folder 23-24)
- Miscellaneous and Hot Leads. (Box-folder 23-25)
- Membership Notes. (Box-folder 23-26)
- Silent Auction Receipts. (Box-folder 23-27)
- Copyright. (Box-folder 23-28)
- Biting the String Snake Information. (Box-folder 23-29)
- Miscellaneous Essays. (Box-folder 23-30)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 23-31)
- Miscellaneous Poetry. (Box-folder 23-32)
- The Road Company Reports (Rough Draft). (Box-folder 23-33)
- Energy Play Notes. (Box-folder 23-34)
- A Hymn to Mother Nature. (Box-folder 23-35)
- The Slave Auction. (Box-folder 23-36)
- Miscellaneous Plays. (Box-folder 23-37 to 23-38 (2 folders))
- Play, untitled. (Box-folder 23-39)
- Descriptions and Press Releases about the Road Company. (Box-folder 23-40)
- Poetry, untitled. (Box-folder 23-41)
- Whiskey. (Box-folder 23-42 to 23-43 (2 folders))
- Four Men and a Monster. (Box-folder 23-44)
- Heroes, Hot Dogs, and Apple Pie. (Box-folder 23-45)
- Unidentified Play. (Box-folder 23-46)
- Momentary Art. (Box-folder 23-47)
- Presenting Possibilities. (Box-folder 23-48 to 23-49 (2 folders))
- Playwriting. (Box-folder 23-50)
- Volunteer Information. (Box-folder 23-51)
- Announcement of Performance "Ce Nitram Sacul." (Box-folder 23-52)
- Pictures from "Happy Days." (Box-folder 24-1)
- Bread Puppet. (Box-folder 24-2)
- Production History. (Box-folder 24-3)
- Plans for Building a Theater in Johnson City. (Box-folder 24-4 to 24-5 (2 folders))
- Article of Computer Viruses. (Box-folder 24-6)
- Credit Card Application. (Box-folder 24-7)
- Business Campaign: Bear Facts. (Box-folder 24-8)
- Advertisements. (Box-folder 24-9)
- Automobile Information. (Box-folder 24-10)
- Benefits and Pension. (Box-folder 24-11)
- Board of Directors Information (Box-folder 24-12)
- Process of Production. (Box-folder 24-13)
- Access America (Long Distance Company). (Box-folder 24-14)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 24-15)
- A Change (Raw Material). (Box-folder 24-16)
- Tour Information Books. (Box-folder 24-17)
- Sponsor Lists. (Box-folder 24-18)
- Texas Commission for the Arts. (Box-folder 24-19)
- Echoes Research Material. (Box-folder 24-20)
- Mailing Lists. (Box-folder 24-21)
- The Road Company Logo. (Box-folder 24-22)
- Thank you Cards. (Box-folder 24-23)
- To God be Glory--Cast List. (Box-folder 24-24)
- Fundraising and Telephone Speeches. (Box-folder 24-25)
- Class Assignments. (Box-folder 24-26)
- Pictures from "Cauc'lld Destiny." (Box-folder 24-27)
- Pictures from "Havel." (Box-folder 24-28)
- Pictures from "Voices of the Prairie." (Box-folder 24-29)
- Box Office Procedures. (Box-folder 24-30)
- Contact Numbers. (Box-folder 24-31)
- "Little Chicago" (Home Season). (Box-folder 24-32)
- AIDS Brochures. (Box-folder 24-33)
- Videos and Audiocassettes of Productions. (Box 25)
- Videos and Audiocassettes of Productions. (Box 26)
- 2008 Accession (Folder 1)
  - Show posters (in alphabetical order by show title)
- 2015 Accession (Box 27)
  - June 1994 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Misc. Work (Box-folder 27-2)
  - 1993/1994 Tax Reports (Box-folder 27-3)
  - 1993/1994 Budget (Box-folder 27-4)
  - Echoes Contracts (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Community Service-Clinton Plan (Box-folder 27-6)
  - July 1993 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - August 1993 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - September 1993 (Box-folder 27-9)
  - October 1993 (Box-folder 27-10)
  - November 1993 (Box-folder 27-11)
  - December 1993 (Box-folder 27-12)
  - January 1994 (Box-folder 27-13)
  - February 1994 (Box-folder 27-14)
  - March 1994 (Box-folder 27-15)
  - April 1994 (Box-folder 27-16)
  - May 1994 (Box-folder 27-17)
  - Financial documents, 1998 (Box-folder 27-18)
  - GL Chart of Accounts (Box-folder 27-19)